Cioni, Peter J. Labor Agreement Collection 5916
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VIII. UNION PAMPHLETS
  - Sub-Series B. UNION PAMPHLETS, BROCHURES, MISCELLANEOUS PUBLICATIONS
    - Printing and Graphic Communications Union. Introducing... brochure, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 32)
      no date
    - Steelworkers of America, United. Pamphlets [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1984; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Item 1: All About Us... Our Services, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 33)
        8pp. nd.
    - Steelworkers of America, United. Pamphlets [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1984; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 34)
      April 1982. 88 pp
      - Item 1: Political Action for Steelworkers, 1982; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 34)
        April 1982. 88 pp.
    - Teamsters, International Brotherhood of. Brochure, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Union Label & Service Trades Department, AFL-CIO. Flyers, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Strike and Negotiating Leaflets, 1970-1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Series IX. MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Unidentified photographs, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Photographs, 1958-1975; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 39)
    1) Coffee break at Picket Post, East Gate, 1958; 2) Main Gate - 4/9/62; 3) Plant in California, March 28, 1975 closeout; 4) 2 misc. unidentified
  - Photographs: Fort Wayne Works, 1952-1974; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Slides: Clark Equipment Co. - Jackson, Michigan, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Statement of US President on NIRA, Pamphlet (Box 5)